American Council for Emigres in the Professions; Records ger017
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP, Undated; 4; originals - 1160 individual files
  - Cernosvitov, Leo, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 44)
  - Chabauty, Claude, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 45)
  - Chalasinski, Joseph, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 46)
  - Charmatz, Richard, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 47)
  - Chartier, Emile, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 48)
  - Chatton, Edoward, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 49)
  - Chaudon, Maurice, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 50)
  - Chiaromonte, Nicola, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 51)
  - Chi-Fang, Li, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 52)
  - Cohen, Gustave, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 53)
  - Cohn, David, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 54)
  - Cohn, Egon, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 55)
  - Cohn, Ernest J., Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 56)
  - Cohn, Sigmund, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 57)
  - Cohn, Walter, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 58)
  - Cohn, Werner, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 59)
  - Cohn, William, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 60)
  - Collando, German, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 61)
  - Combaire-Sylvain, Suzanne, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 62)
  - Committee on Work Relief for Refugees, Undated
  - Conrad-Martius, Hedwig, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 63)
  - Cooper, Emile, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 64)
  - Cornelissen, Frederic, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 65)
  - Cornil, Paul, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 66)
  - Cuevas, Miguel, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 67)
  - Curtius, Ludwig, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 68)
  - Czechowicz, Paul, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 69)
  - Daniel, Ludwig, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 70)
  - Darmstaedter, Friedrich, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 71)
  - Daube, David, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 72)
  - Daus, Hedwig, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 73)
  - David, Constantin, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 74)
  - David, K. J., Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 75)
  - David, Martin, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 76)
  - Davidogg, M. [von], Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 77)
  - Deanovic, Mirko, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 78)
  - Debre, Michel, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 79)
  - Delsarte, Jean, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 80)
  - Demant, Viktor, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 81)
  - Demus, Otto, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 82)
  - Deryng, Antoni, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 83)
  - Dessau, Paul, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 84)
  - Dessauer, Friedrich, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 85)
  - Diaz, Diego, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 86)
  - Diehl, Charles, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 87)
  - Dienes, Paul, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 88)
  - Diestel, Dr, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 89)
  - Dieudonne, Jean, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 90)
  - DiNola, A., Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 91)
  - Diringer, David, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 92)
  - Dobretsberger, Joseph, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 93)
  - Doery, Iwan, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 94)
  - Dominguez, Jose M., Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 95)
  - Domke, Martin, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 96)
  - Doroszewski, Witold, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 97)
  - Driesch, Hans, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 98)
  - Drucker, Ernst, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 99)
  - Dub, Alfredo, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 100)
  - Duncker, Karl, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 101)
  - Du Nouy, Pierre Lecomte, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 102)
  - Duyvendak, J. J. L., Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 103)
  - Duyvis, F. Donker, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 104)
  - Dvoicenco, Dr, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 105)
  - Dvornik, Frantisek, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 106)
  - Eberhard, Wolfram, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 107)
  - Eberman, Ludwik, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 108)
  - Eckardt, Hans von, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 109)
  - Eckstein, Walther, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 110)
  - Ehrenberg, Hans, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 111)
  - Ehrenberg, Victor, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 112)
  - Ehrenhaft, Felix, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 113)
  - Ehrenstein, Albert, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 114)
  - Ehrenzweig, Albert, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 115)
  - Ehresmann, Charles, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 116)
  - Ehrlich, Ludwik, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 117)
  - Eichner, Charles, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 118)
  - Eisenmann, Charles, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 119)
  - Eisner, Paul, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 120)
  - Elias, Norbert, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 121)
  - Eliashevich, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 122)
  - Emsheimer, Ernst, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 123)
  - Engel-Janosi, Friedrich, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 124)
  - Engel, Salo, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 125)
  - Ephrussi, Boris, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 126)
  - Eppstein, Paul, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 127)
  - Epstein, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 128)
  - Erculisse, Paul, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 129)
  - Erkes, Eduard, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 130)
  - Ernst, Max, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 131)
  - Ernst, Paul, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 132)
  - Eros, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 133)
  - Eszlary, Charles, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 134)
  - Eulenburg, Franz, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 135)
  - Fabre, Monsieur, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 136)
  - Fajrajzen, Stefano, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 137)
  - Falco, Giorgio, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 138)
  - Falk, Eugen, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 139)
  - Faludi, Eugenio, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 140)
  - Farmer, Albert J., Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 141)
  - Fay, Bernard, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 142)
  - Feder, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 143)
  - Fehr, Oskar, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 144)
  - Feigl, Fritz, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 145)
  - Feldmann, Clarence, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 146)
  - Feldmann, Leon, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 147)
  - Felhendler, M., Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 148)
  - Felipe, Elena, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 149)
  - Fenchel, Werner, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 150)
  - Fernandez, Guillermo, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 151)
  - Ferrero, G., Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 152)
  - Feuchtwanger, Ludwig, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 153)
  - Fink, Eugen, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 154)
  - Finkelkraut, Jerzy, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 155)
  - Finzi, Leo A., Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 156)
  - Finzi, Marcello, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 157)
  - Fischer, Hugo, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 158)
  - Fischer, Josef L., Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 159)
  - Flamm, Peter, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 160)
  - Flatow, Georg, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 161)
  - Flechtheim, Ossip K., Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 162)
  - Fleg, Edmond, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 163)
  - Fleischer, Arthur, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 164)
  - Fleischmann, Benno, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 165)
  - Fleischmann, Hugo R., Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 166)
  - Fleischmann, Max, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 167)
  - Flesch, Carl, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 168)
  - Florovsky, Anthony, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 169)
  - Fodor, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 170)
  - Fogelson, S., Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 171)
  - Fonck, Charles M, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 172)
  - Forchheimer, Karl, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 173)
  - Forgac, A., Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 174)
  - Fraenkel, Ernest, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 175)
  - Fraenkel, Ernst M., Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 176)
  - Fraenkl, Pavel, Undated (Box 2 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 177)
  - Francastel, Pierre, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 1)
  - Frank, Simeon, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 2)
  - Frankenau-Bloch, Hedwig, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 3)
  - Frankenstein, Ernst, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 4)
  - Frankl, Liselotte, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 5)
  - Freud, J., Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 6)
  - Freudenthal, Hans, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 7)
  - Freund, Stefan, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 8)
  - Fried, Ernst Hans, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 9)
  - Friedlaender, H.F., Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 10)
  - Friedmann, Friedrich, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 11)
  - Friedmann, Georges, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 12)
  - Friedmann, Wilhelm, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 13)
  - Frijda, Alfons, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 14)
  - Frisch, Otto Robert, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 15)
  - Frisch, Raanar, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 16)
  - Froehlich, Walter H., Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 17)
  - Fröhlich, Ervin, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 18)
  - Fröhlich-Bume, Lilli, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 19)
  - Fubini, Mario, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 20)
  - Fubini, Renzo, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 21)
  - Fuchs, Richard, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 22)
  - Fumet, Stanislaus, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 23)
  - Fuerth, Reinhold, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 24)
  - Furtmueller, Lux Ernst, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 25)
  - Gal, Hans, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 26)
  - Garcia, Enrique, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 27)
  - Garcia, Jose, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 28)
  - Gaupp, Fritz, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 29)
  - Geiger, Bernhard, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 30)
  - Geiger, Theodore, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 31)
  - Geiringer, Karl, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 32)
  - Gerely, Tibor, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 33)
  - Gerson, Ernest, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 34)
  - Gerstenberg, Ernst, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 35)
  - Gese, Gertrud, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 36)
  - Geyer, Emil, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 37)
  - Gilson, Etienne, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 38)
  - Ginzburg, Leone, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 39)
  - Giraud, Emil (alias Louis Masson), Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 40)
  - Gladstein, Tunia M., Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 41)
  - Glas, Richard, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 42)
  - Glaser, Curt, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 43)
  - Glucksman, Stefan, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 44)
  - Goetz, Oswald, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 45)
  - Goldenberg, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 46)
  - Goldenweiser, Alexis, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 47)
  - Goldmann, Emil, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 48)
  - Goldschmidt, Lazarus, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 49)
  - Goldschmidt, Viktor Moritz, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 50)
  - Goldstein, Ladislas, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 51)
  - Gorny, Ajzyk, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 52)
  - Gorodetzky, Serge, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 53)
  - Gougenheim, Georges, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 54)
  - Gourevitch, Gregoire, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 55)
  - Gourou, Pierre, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 56)
  - Grabar, Pierre, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 57)
  - Grabowsky, Adolf, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 58)
  - Gradenwitz, Alfred, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 59)
  - Graeff, Werner, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 60)
  - Granet, Marcel, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 61)
  - de Greef, Etienne, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 62)
  - Grelling, Kurt, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 63)
  - Groer, F., Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 64)
  - Groethuysen, Bernard, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 65)
  - de Groot, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 66)
  - Gros, Andre, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 67)
  - Gross, Philip, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 68)
  - Grossman, Henry, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 69)
  - Gruenhut, Max, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 70)
  - Grumach, Ernst, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 71)
  - Grunberg, Michel, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 72)
  - Grunberg, Walther, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 73)
  - Grunebaum, Gustav von, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 74)
  - Grunwald, Geza and Tibor, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 75)
  - Gueroult, Martial, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 76)
  - Guilhon, Etienne, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 77)
  - Guillaume, Paul, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 78)
  - Guillemin, Henri, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 79)
  - Gulkowitsch, Lazar, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 80)
  - Gumbel, Emil, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 81)
  - Guenther, Gotthard, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 82)
  - Gutfeld, Dr, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 83)
  - Gutmann, Rene, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 84)
  - Haas, Alice, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 85)
  - Haesart, J. P., Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 86)
  - Hagemejer, Wlodzimierz, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 87)
  - Hahn, Marie, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 88)
  - Haim, Joseph, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 89)
  - Hajek, Leo, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 90)
  - Halberstadt, Siegfried, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 91)
  - Halberstaedter, Agnes, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 92)
  - Halecki, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 93)
  - Halevy, Elie, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 94)
  - Haller-Jarislowsky, Johanna, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 95)
  - Halm, Georg, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 96)
  - Halphan, Louis, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 97)
  - Halwachs, Maurice, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 98)
  - Hamburger, Martin, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 99)
  - Hamori, Laszlo, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 100)
  - Harand, Irene, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 101)
  - Harcourt, Robert, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 102)
  - Harms, Ernst, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 103)
  - Hartmannshenn, Herta, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 104)
  - Hartogs, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 105)
  - Hartogson-Sonin, Berte, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 106)
  - Haspels, Emilie, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 107)
  - Hayek, Friedrich A. von, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 108)
  - Haymann, Undated (Box 3 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 109)